

9903807991



royamit833@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/amit -roy-232169171/



Howrah, West Bengal



## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML

CSS

JavaScript / TypeScript / ES6

Angular 6+

React JS

Node JS (3 months)

Firebase/MySQL

Git/Bitbucket

JIRA

### **EDUCATION**

MCA (Pursuing)

IGNOU

ST. Xavier's College (2018-2022)

**B.Sc.** (Hon's in Computer Science)

Calcutta University

N.D College (2013-2017)

Score - 55.25%

**HIGHER SECONDARY (12th)** 

WBCHSE - 2011-2013

Score - 71.40%

SECONDARY (10th)

WBBSE - 2011

Score - 78.37%

# **AMIT ROY**

### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a full-stack developer with 3 years of work experience in Angular, React and little bit in Node JS. I worked both as a frontend developer as well as backend API developer. I am a quick learner and an easily adaptable person. I look forward to working in an organization where I can enhance my technical skills as well as prove myself as a useful resource.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Company: DreamzTech Solutions - 08/2021 - Present

- **1.** Face Valued Web Application: It is an online doctor consultation site where any patients can share their disease with registered doctor and booking their appointment.
- <u>Technologies:</u> It is based on React JS in frontend as well as Node JS and firebase for backend API. I am working in React JS and some API section in Node JS.
- **2.** <u>S&IB Web Application:</u> It is basically an ERP system. Its provides services of Total Security Solutions, Integrated Facility Management, Outsourced Banking Services, Housekeeping, CCTV, Payroll Management etc.
- <u>Technologies:</u> It is based on Angular 8 as well as .Net in backend. I am working as a frontend developer in Angular.
- **3.** <u>Wahoo Games:</u> It is a betting site, where lots of games are available. User can play and bet in each and every game and win money.
- <u>Technologies:</u> It is based on Angular 13 for frontend and .Net for backend API. I am working as a frontend developer in Angular.

**Company:** Softclique Software Services LLP – 04/2019 to 07/2021

- **1.** <u>Eventbaja Web Application:</u> An upcoming event management platform for Marriage, Birthday party and other events.
- <u>Technologies:</u> It is based on Angular 8+ in frontend section and Laravel with MySQL for backend rest API, as a part of a 4 members team.
- **2.** <u>Eventbaja App:</u> An upcoming event management platform for Marriage, Birthday party and other events.
- <u>Technologies:</u> It is based on Ionic 4 in frontend section and Laravel with MySQL for backend rest API, as a part of a 4 members team.

<sup>\*</sup> I hereby declare that the details furnished above are true and correct to the best of my knowledge.